[
  {
    "question": "What type of app helps you to get work done, such as word processors, spreadsheets, and presentation apps?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Productivity app",
      "c. Communication app",
      "b. Entertainment app",
      "d. Business app"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. Productivity app"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of display uses liquid crystals to create images?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Retina",
      "c. AMOLED",
      "b. OLED",
      "d. LCD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. LCD"
  },
  {
    "question": "The display is the screen that you use to interact with the mobile device.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of an AAA server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. To store and forward email messages between                                            users",
      "c. To provide authentication, authorization,                                            and accounting services for users on a network",
      "b. To manage printing jobs for users on a network",
      "d. To collect and analyze data about network                                            traffic and performance"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "c. To provide authentication, authorization,                                            and accounting services for users on a network"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of accessory protects the mobile device from scratches and damage?",
    "answers": [
      "a. External storage",
      "c. Stylus pen",
      "b. Case",
      "d. Screen protector"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "b. Case"
  },
  {
    "question": "Adobe Illustrator is a popular graphics and multimedia software application that is used to create and edit vector graphics.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of synchronization method allows you to wirelessly synchronize your mobile device with other devices?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Bluetooth                                            synchronization",
      "c. Cloud synchronization",
      "b. USB synchronization",
      "d. All of the above"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. Bluetooth                                            synchronization"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of display uses organic light-emitting diodes to create images?",
    "answers": [
      "a. LCD",
      "c. AMOLED",
      "b. OLED",
      "d. Retina"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "b. OLED"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mobile device's battery can be replaced by the user",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Web servers can be used to host web applications, such as CRM systems and ERP systems.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some examples of popular web servers?",
    "answers": [
      "a. IIS",
      "c. Nginx",
      "b. Apache",
      "d. All of the above"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most popular AAA server software?",
    "answers": [
      "a. FreeRADIUS",
      "c. All of the above",
      "b. Microsoft RADIUS Server",
      "d. Cisco ISE"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. Cisco ISE"
  },
  {
    "question": "ERP software is used to manage the core business processes of a business, such as accounting, manufacturing, and sales.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most common type of file server",
    "answers": [
      "a. Windows Server",
      "c. FreeNAS",
      "b. Linux",
      "d. macOS Server"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. Windows Server"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of synchronization method allows you to connect your mobile device to your computer and synchronize your data using a USB cable?",
    "answers": [
      "a. USB synchronization",
      "c. Cloud                                            synchronization",
      "b. All of the above",
      "d. Bluetooth synchronization"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. USB synchronization"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the benefits of using a network monitoring server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Optimize network performance",
      "c. Identify and troubleshoot network problems",
      "b. Plan for future network growth",
      "d. All of the above"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the brain of the mobile device?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Memory",
      "c. Storage",
      "b. Display",
      "d. Processor"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. Processor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of accessory allows you to expand the storage capacity of the mobile device?",
    "answers": [
      "a. External storage",
      "c. Screen protector",
      "b. Stylus pen",
      "d. Case"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. External storage"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of accessory allows you to interact with the mobile device more precisely?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Case",
      "c. Screen protector",
      "b. Stylus pen",
      "d. External storage"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "b. Stylus pen"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of memory stores the data and code that is being used by the processor?",
    "answers": [
      "a. RAM",
      "c. Display",
      "b. ROM",
      "d. Storage"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. RAM"
  },
  {
    "question": "The battery provides power to the mobile device.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of accessory allows you to charge the mobile device on the go?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Case",
      "c. Stylus pen",
      "b. Screen protector",
      "d. Portable charger"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. Portable charger"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a web server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. To authenticate users and grant or deny                                            access to resources",
      "c. To store and deliver web pages to users                                            over the internet",
      "b. To collect and analyze data about network                                            traffic and performance",
      "d. To manage printing jobs for users on a                                            network"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "c. To store and deliver web pages to users                                            over the internet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of business software helps businesses manage their customer interactions?",
    "answers": [
      "a. CRM                                            software",
      "c. SCM software",
      "b. All of the above",
      "d. ERP software"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. CRM                                            software"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the benefits of using an AAA server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. All of the above",
      "c. Increased manageability",
      "b. Reduced IT costs",
      "d. Improved security"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Graphics and multimedia software can be used to create and edit images, videos, and audio files.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of synchronization service stores your data in the cloud and makes it available on all of your devices?",
    "answers": [
      "a. USB synchronization",
      "c. All of the above",
      "b. Cloud synchronization",
      "d. Bluetooth synchronization"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "b. Cloud synchronization"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of accessory protects the display of the mobile device from scratches and fingerprints?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Case",
      "c. Screen protector",
      "b. External storage",
      "d. Stylus pen"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "c. Screen protector"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the benefits of using a file server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Reduced IT costs",
      "c. Easier file sharing and collaborationEasier file sharing and collaboration",
      "b. Centralized file storage and backup",
      "d. All of the above"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of an email server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. To collect and analyze data about network                                            traffic and performance",
      "c. To authenticate users and grant or deny                                            access to resources",
      "b. To store and forward email messages between                                            users",
      "d. To manage printing jobs for users on a                                            network"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "b. To store and forward email messages between                                            users"
  },
  {
    "question": "Network monitoring servers can be used to monitor the performance of network devices, such as routers and switches.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most popular web server software in the world?",
    "answers": [
      "a. IIS",
      "c. Apache",
      "b. Nginx",
      "d. All of the above"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main purpose of a file server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. To manage printing jobs for users on a                                            network",
      "c. To collect and analyze data about network                                            traffic and performance",
      "b. To authenticate users and grant or deny                                            access to resources",
      "d. To                                            store and provide access to files for users on a network"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. To                                            store and provide access to files for users on a network"
  },
  {
    "question": "CRM software is used to track and manage customer interactions.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "AAA servers can be used to implement multi-factor authentication (MFA) to improve security.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some examples of popular email servers?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Outlook.com",
      "c. Gmail",
      "b. All of the above",
      "d. Exchange"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "b. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is important to only install apps from trusted sources, such as the official app stores for your device.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most popular email server software for businesses?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Google Workspace",
      "c. All of the above",
      "b. Microsoft Exchange",
      "d. Microsoft Office 365"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. Microsoft Office 365"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a network monitoring server?",
    "answers": [
      "a. To manage printing jobs for users on a                                            network",
      "c. To store and forward email messages between                                            users",
      "b. To authenticate users and grant or deny                                            access to resources",
      "d. To collect and analyze data about network                                            traffic and performance"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "d. To collect and analyze data about network                                            traffic and performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of app allows you to communicate with others, such as messaging apps, social media apps, and video conferencing apps?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Business app",
      "c. Communication app",
      "b. Productivity app",
      "d. Entertainment app"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "c. Communication app"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most popular network monitoring server software?",
    "answers": [
      "a. Zabbix",
      "c. All of the above",
      "b. Prometheus",
      "d. Nagios"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "c. All of the above"
  }
]